<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<advisories>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>00:00</gmt>
		<vt>30</vt>
		<rf>16</rf>
		<obs>Diminishing production of pyroclastic flows in the Tar River valley &#13;Seismic activity is increasing &#13;A period of reduced activity at Soufrière Hills </obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>01:00</gmt>
		<vt>12</vt>
		<rf>16</rf>
		<obs>Dome complex has reached its highest volume &#13;Frequent VT earthquake swarms</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>02:00</gmt>
		<vt>36</vt>
		<rf>12</rf>
		<obs>Explosive dome collapse was initiated, triggered by further mass removal associated with possible pyroclastic flow formation</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>03:00</gmt>
		<vt>22</vt>
		<rf>18</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>04:00</gmt>
		<vt>28</vt>
		<rf>22</rf>
		<obs>A probable increase in pyroclastic flow production triggering intense explosive activity with asymmetric projection of large projectiles to the NE and the formation of a 14 km eruption column, and the dispersal of pumiceous and lithic tephra-fall over much of the south of the island</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>05:00</gmt>
		<vt>33</vt>
		<rf>17</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>06:00</gmt>
		<vt>18</vt>
		<rf>22</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>07:00</gmt>
		<vt>21</vt>
		<rf>25</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>08:00</gmt>
		<vt>23</vt>
		<rf>28</rf>
		<obs>Ash clouds surrounding Soufrière Hills make it increasingly more difficult to visually monitor the events occurring at Soufrière Hills</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>09:00</gmt>
		<vt>37</vt>
		<rf>28</rf>
		<obs>Formation of many pyroclastic flows in the Tar River valley.</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>10:00</gmt>
		<vt>42</vt>
		<rf>21</rf>
		<obs>Semi-continuous pyroclastic flow production into the Tar River valley progressively unroofed the eastern flank of the dome.</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>11:00</gmt>
		<vt>20</vt>
		<rf>18</rf>
		<obs>Continuous ash fall in Plymouth area</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>12:00</gmt>
		<vt>32</vt>
		<rf>22</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>13:00</gmt>
		<vt>50</vt>
		<rf>20</rf>
		<obs></obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>14:00</gmt>
		<vt>12</vt>
		<rf>16</rf>
		<obs>Soufrière Hills erupts for approximately, 1 hour. Extensive pyroclastic flows are heading east down the Tar Valley and west toward Plymouth city at rapid speeds</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>15:00</gmt>
		<vt></vt>
		<rf></rf>
		<obs>No Report</obs>
	</advisory>
	<advisory>
		<gmt>16:00</gmt>
		<vt></vt>
		<rf></rf>
		<obs>No Report</obs>
	</advisory>
</advisories>